<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Crimson Kindness</title>
    <link>https://crimsonkindness.github.io/about/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Crimson Kindness</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 18:02:49 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://crimsonkindness.github.io/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://crimsonkindness.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 18:02:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crimsonkindness.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Crimson Kindness was founded in February of 2013 out of a desire to make our
campus a more kind place. Inspired by the Random Acts of Kindness Foundation,
Crimson Kindness set out to make a difference on campus and in the Tuscaloosa
community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-mission&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of Crimson Kindness on The University of Alabama campus is to create a
community of kindness by engaging the student population in acts of kindness and
inspiring kindness in our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;why-does-the-university-of-alabama-need-an-organization-like-crimson-kindness&#34;&gt;Why does The University of Alabama need an organization like Crimson Kindness?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone can benefit from kindness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kindness promotes personal interactions between students&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engaging in acts of kindness facilitates personal development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kindness makes a positive impact on the campus and community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-will-crimson-kindness-achieve-their-goal&#34;&gt;How will Crimson Kindness achieve their goal?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By encouraging individual actions of kindness across campus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By organizing group kindness events and initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By using online social media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By inspiring the community to be more kind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-we-do&#34;&gt;What We Do&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-meetings&#34;&gt;The Meetings&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All our members come together and talk about what is coming up in CK and how to
help out. We discuss our events in the following weeks, get our members excited
about kindness, and prep for upcoming events. Our meetings typically occur every
2 weeks, and alternate between general meetings and social meetings. Check our
Meetings page to see when the next meeting is!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-teams&#34;&gt;The Teams&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teams are a fun way for you to engage in acts of kindness in a small group setting.
The Team Leader will bring an activity to complete each meeting so you can go do
little acts of kindness with your team. Teams meet every other week. There is a
team meeting available every evening (Sunday-Thursday) during team weeks. You
can choose the night that works best for you! If you miss your team meeting
though, you are welcome to attend a different one that week. We do ask that you
become a member before you become a part of a team. Find out more and sign up
on our Teams page!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-projects&#34;&gt;The Projects&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We schedule about 2 projects per month for our members to get involved. Sometimes
it’s an event or initiative. These projects are announced at our meetings and are
posted to our &lt;a href=&#34;http://facebook.com/CrimsonKindness&#34;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/CrimsonKindness&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; pages. You can check out what we
currently have planned on our What We Do page. We can’t wait to see you at our next event!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to join?&lt;/strong&gt; Click over to our Join page to learn how you can become a
member of Crimson Kindness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to meet our leaders?&lt;/strong&gt; Head on over to the &lt;a href=&#34;../officers&#34;&gt;Officers&lt;/a&gt; or Team Leaders page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>