<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Applies on Crimson Kindness</title>
    <link>https://crimsonkindness.github.io/apply/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Applies on Crimson Kindness</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 18:18:06 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://crimsonkindness.github.io/apply/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Apply for the 2017-18 Leadership Team</title>
      <link>https://crimsonkindness.github.io/apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 18:18:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crimsonkindness.github.io/apply/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;be-the-change-you-want-to-see-in-the-world-gandhi&#34;&gt;“Be the change you want to see in the world.” ~Gandhi&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest in becoming a future leader of Crimson Kindness. Please
read each document relevant to the position you are applying for. See below for Frequently Asked Questions about the
application process for becoming an officer or team leader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All applications are due Tuesday, March 21 at 11:59PM.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;officers-faq&#34;&gt;Officers FAQ&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-many-officer-positions-are-available&#34;&gt;How many officer positions are available?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are 7 officer positions available for next academic year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-long-is-my-term-as-an-officer&#34;&gt;How long is my term as an officer?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being an officer is a year long commitment beginning in April.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;are-there-any-basic-requirements-to-be-an-officer&#34;&gt;Are there any basic requirements to be an officer?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Per the University’s guidelines, officers are required to have a minimum 2.0 GPA and be in good standing with the University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;do-i-have-to-be-a-current-member-to-apply&#34;&gt;Do I have to be a current member to apply?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. If you are new to Crimson Kindness or are just hearing about us you are still welcome to apply. While we prefer to see members of our organization become leaders, we will consider applicants with strong leadership qualities and specific skill sets to bring to our organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-i-learn-more-about-being-an-officer&#34;&gt;How do I learn more about being an officer?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All other information regarding the positions available, descriptions of positions, and timeline for applying are found in the Officer Information document.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-is-the-deadline-for-the-application-to-be-submitted&#34;&gt;What is the deadline for the application to be submitted?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deadline to submit the application is Tuesday, March 21 at 11:59PM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;do-i-have-to-do-an-interview&#34;&gt;Do I have to do an interview?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interviews are required for applicants that proceed to the next round. There is more information regarding the interview on the application. If you are selected to interview, we will email you that information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;team-leader-faq&#34;&gt;Team Leader FAQ&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-many-team-leader-positions-are-there&#34;&gt;How many team leader positions are there?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will have 5 team leaders for the fall semester. Everyone who is interested is encouraged to apply. Should the need arise, those not initially chosen as one of the 5 may be contacted to lead a team in the fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-long-will-i-be-a-team-leader&#34;&gt;How long will I be a team leader?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a team leader is a one semester commitment (Fall 2017) and team leaders are welcome to apply again each semester.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-i-learn-more-about-being-a-team-leader&#34;&gt;How do I learn more about being a team leader?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All other information regarding the team leader positions are found in the Team Leader Information document.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-is-the-deadline-for-the-application-to-be-submitted-1&#34;&gt;What is the deadline for the application to be submitted?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deadline to submit the application is Tuesday, March 21 at 11:59PM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;do-i-have-to-do-an-interview-1&#34;&gt;Do I have to do an interview?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No interview is required.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>